Contact

thomasankcorn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/thomasankcorn-370889151 (LinkedIn) ankcorn.xyz (Personal) github.com/ThomasAnkcorn (Portfolio)

Top Skills

React

Node.js

Javascript

Thomas Ankcorn

Coaching teams in Node.js and React

London, Greater London, United Kingdom

Summary

Highly motivated software engineer working in London. I'm passionate about building products and coaching software engineers. I have a wide range of skills across the technology stack as well as experience of systems architecture and engaging successfully with clients.

I'm continuously focussed on self-improvement. Currently, I am actively developing my knowledge of kubernetes.

Experience

BAE Systems Applied Intelligence 2 years 11 months

DevOps Chapter Lead October 2018 - Present

London, United Kingdom

- Provides technical assurance, guidance and coaching for 6 teams and 30 developers, creating a supportive environment focused on learning and development.
- Senior Software Engineer.
- Embeds in teams to do CI/CD Pipeline Architecture and Setup.
- Supports architecture team on the adoption of the next generation of Javascript tools to increase agility and DevX.

Lead Developer April 2018 - October 2018 (7 months)

Software Developer July 2016 - April 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Education

The University of Sheffield

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Automatic Control and Systems Engineering \cdot (2012 - 2016)